{
    "id": "7309b9d2fe764d9f91cefa0d25280e0a",
    "title": "Grammar exercise: which word is wrong?",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1e547e36e4ac42718f8cb7ecfd0311dd",
            "title": "Omission Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Take the book with you in case you will see Mary.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "in case",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Thatâ€™s the house where he was born in.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "where",
                        "was",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She had died a couple of years ago.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had",
                        "a",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He asked that what I was doing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "what",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He asked to her why she was angry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "why",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I will go to Mexico, I will see him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "to",
                        "when"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is very much angry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Yesterday in the evening he came to dinner.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in the",
                        "came",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is my friend who he was at school with me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "he",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Supposing if you fail, what will you do?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "fail",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}